<resources>
    <!-- Affirmations -->
    <string name="app_name">Antichamber Affirmations</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">Every journey is a series of choices. The first is to begin the journey.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">Patience has its own rewards.</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Taking the first step can be harder than the rest of the challenge.</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Many small obstacles can make for one large problem.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">Some choices leave us running around a lot without really getting anywhere.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Live on your own watch, not on someone else\'s.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">Failing to succeed does not mean failing to progress.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">Some paths are clearer than others.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Some paths are straight forward.</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">A choice may be as simple as going left or going right.</string>
    <string name="affirmation11">The choice doesn\'t matter if the outcome is the same.</string>
    <string name="affirmation12">If you don\'t like where you\'ve ended up, try doing something else.</string>
    <string name="affirmation13">When you return to where you have been, things aren\'t always as remembered.</string>
    <string name="affirmation14">We fall down when there is nothing there to support us.</string>
    <string name="affirmation15">Building a bridge can get you over a problem.</string>
    <string name="affirmation16">Some hurdles are too high to jump over.</string>
    <string name="affirmation17">Life is full of ups and downs.</string>
    <string name="affirmation18">Connecting the pieces can solve a puzzle.</string>
    <string name="affirmation19">Life has a way of pushing us in the right direction.</string>
    <string name="affirmation20">The end may come before we were ready to get there.</string>
    <string name="affirmation21">Life isn\'t about getting to the end.</string>
    <string name="affirmation22">It\'s harder to progress if you\'re leaving things behind.</string>
    <string name="affirmation23">The further we get, the less help we need.</string>
    <string name="affirmation24">Moving forward may require making the most of what you\'ve got.</string>
    <string name="affirmation25">Some tasks require a lot of care and observation.</string>
    <string name="affirmation26">Taking one path often means missing out on another.</string>
    <string name="affirmation27">A path may not be right or wrong. It may just be different.</string>
    <string name="affirmation28">Look a little harder, and you will find a way forward.</string>
    <string name="affirmation29">Venturing into the unknown can lead to great rewards.</string>
    <string name="affirmation30">If you\'re only focusing on right now, you won\'t have enough for later.</string>
    <string name="affirmation31">A dead end will only stop you if you don\'t try to move through it.</string>
    <string name="affirmation32">Going a certain way may require building your own path.</string>
    <string name="affirmation33">There\'s nothing wrong with taking shortcuts.</string>
    <string name="affirmation34">We often fall into things when we least expect.</string>
    <string name="affirmation35">What looks out of reach may only be a few steps away.</string>
    <string name="affirmation36">There are multiple ways to approach a situation.</string>
    <string name="affirmation37">When you\'ve hit rock bottom, the only way is up.</string>
    <string name="affirmation38">Some outcomes are more favorable than others.</string>
    <string name="affirmation39">How we perceive a problem can change every time we see it.</string>
    <string name="affirmation40">The solution to a problem may just require a more thorough look at it.</string>
    <string name="affirmation41">Rushing through a problem won\'t always give the right results.</string>
    <string name="affirmation42">Moving through a problem slower may help find the solution.</string>
    <string name="affirmation43">If you never stop trying, you will get there eventually.</string>
    <string name="affirmation44">Raw persistence may be the only option other than giving up entirely.</string>
    <string name="affirmation45">Some problems just come down to size.</string>
    <string name="affirmation46">A problem may only be difficult when you are missing the right tools.</string>
    <string name="affirmation47">What we\'ve done before may impact what we can do next.</string>
    <string name="affirmation48">If you aren\'t paying attention, you will miss everything around you.</string>
    <string name="affirmation49">Some choices can leave us running around in circles.</string>
    <string name="affirmation50">Splitting a problem up may help you find the answer.</string>
    <string name="affirmation51">What appears impossible may have a very simple answer.</string>
    <string name="affirmation52">If you lose sight of what\'s important, it may not be there when you need it.</string>
    <string name="affirmation53">Too much curiosity can get the best of us.</string>
    <string name="affirmation54">Signs may be helping you more than you realize.</string>
    <string name="affirmation55">Understanding a problem requires filling in the pieces.</string>
    <string name="affirmation56">Small steps can take you great distances.</string>
    <string name="affirmation57">The path of least resistance is a valid option.</string>
    <string name="affirmation58">No matter how high you climb, there\'s always more to achieve.</string>
    <string name="affirmation59">Falling down teaches us how to get up and try again.</string>
    <string name="affirmation60">The world rarely changes when we watch to see it happen.</string>
    <string name="affirmation61">Half way through is half way finished.</string>
    <string name="affirmation62">The problem may not be where you\'re going, but how to get there.</string>
    <string name="affirmation63">New skills enable further progress.</string>
    <string name="affirmation64">Mastering a skill requires practice.</string>
    <string name="affirmation65">A little kind direction can get obstacles out of your way.</string>
    <string name="affirmation66">Solving a problem may require approaching it from a different angle.</string>
    <string name="affirmation67">Try hard enough and you will get to where you want to be.</string>
    <string name="affirmation68">Some doors will close unless we hold them open.</string>
    <string name="affirmation69">When you absorb your surroundings, you may notice things that you didn\'t see before.</string>
    <string name="affirmation70">Dig a little deeper and you may find something new.</string>
    <string name="affirmation71">Attention to detail can lead to very rewarding outcomes.</string>
    <string name="affirmation72">Solving a problem may require using abilities that we didn\'t realize we had.</string>
    <string name="affirmation73">Old skills are useful even after we have learned new ones.</string>
    <string name="affirmation74">The right answers may also be the most obvious ones.</string>
    <string name="affirmation75">Some obstacles are more stubborn than others.</string>
    <string name="affirmation76">Some things don\'t have a deeper meaning.</string>
    <string name="affirmation77">The right decisions at the right time will get you where you want to go.</string>
    <string name="affirmation78">Some choices are only useful when we make them early.</string>
    <string name="affirmation79">With forethought, things have a way of just working themselves out.</string>
    <string name="affirmation80">Some challenges are far harder than they first appear.</string>
    <string name="affirmation81">To get past a problem, you may just need to keep pushing through it.</string>
    <string name="affirmation82">Getting to a solution requires cutting out what doesn\'t work.</string>
    <string name="affirmation83">The further we explore, the more connected everything becomes.</string>
    <string name="affirmation84">A window of opportunity can lead to new places if you are willing to take a closer look.</string>
    <string name="affirmation85">The world looks different on the other side.</string>
    <string name="affirmation86">When you have enough resources, you can start growing more.</string>
    <string name="affirmation87">You can grow a garden anywhere.</string>
    <string name="affirmation88">The best solutions may still be the most primitive ones.</string>
    <string name="affirmation89">If you lead the way, others will follow.</string>
    <string name="affirmation90">Straightforward problems can often require roundabout solutions.</string>
    <string name="affirmation91">If you are missing information, it\'s easy to be misled.</string>
    <string name="affirmation92">When you look beyond the surface, there may be more to find.</string>
    <string name="affirmation93">Sometimes we only have just enough to get by.</string>
    <string name="affirmation94">When what you have is not enough, find ways to turn it into more.</string>
    <string name="affirmation95">Getting where we want may require jumping through some hoops.</string>
    <string name="affirmation96">Throwing yourself into things can take you to new heights.</string>
    <string name="affirmation97">Similar problems can have entirely different solutions.</string>
    <string name="affirmation98">Some events happen whether we want them to or not.</string>
    <string name="affirmation99">Old solutions can apply to new problems.</string>
    <string name="affirmation100">The consequences of one choice can cut us off from making others.</string>
    <string name="affirmation101">At times we need to view the world from someone else\'s perspective.</string>
    <string name="affirmation102">Sometimes you need to be carried.</string>
    <string name="affirmation103">There comes a time when you can work your way through anything.</string>
    <string name="affirmation104">With more experience, previous challenges aren\'t so difficult.</string>
    <string name="affirmation105">There\'s no need to take apart what already works.</string>
    <string name="affirmation106">A few steps backwards may keep you moving forwards.</string>
    <string name="affirmation107">Obscure problems may require unusual solutions.</string>
    <string name="affirmation108">Getting to the end requires tying off the loose ends.</string>
    <string name="affirmation109">The world is always finding new ways to surprise us.</string>
    <string name="affirmation110">Sometimes we do things just to go along for the ride.</string>
    <string name="affirmation111">The more we complete, the harder it gets to find what we missed.</string>
    <string name="affirmation112">Some challenges exist just to test how much we know.</string>
    <string name="affirmation113">You can\'t do everything yourself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation114">The world is full of secrets waiting to be uncovered.</string>
    <string name="affirmation115">Peeking behind the curtains lets us see how everything works.</string>
    <string name="affirmation116">Some problems can\'t be solved until you\'re more experienced.</string>
    <string name="affirmation117">We move on when there is nothing left to learn.</string>
    <string name="affirmation118">Complicated problems are easier when solved one step at a time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation119">We can appreciate the entire journey by looking back at how far we have come.</string>
    <string name="affirmation120">Every journey comes to an end.</string>


</resources>